They're back with a twissst.
Zootopia 2 is a animation, comedy, adventure film directed by Jared Bush.
After cracking the biggest case in Zootopia's history, rookie cops Judy Hopps and Nick Wilde find themselves on the
twisting trail of a great mystery when Gary De'Snake arrives and turns the animal metropolis upside down.
To crack the case, Judy and Nick must go undercover to unexpected new parts of
town, where their growing partnership is tested like never before.
Judy Hopps (voice), played by Ginnifer Goodwin.
Nick Wilde (voice), played by Jason Bateman.
Gary De'Snake (voice), played by Ke Huy Quan.
Nibbles Maplestick (voice), played by Fortune Feimster.
Pawbert Lynxley (voice), played by Andy Samberg.
Milton Lynxley (voice), played by David Strathairn.
Zootopia 2 (titled Zootropolis 2 among other titles in some markets) is a 2025 American animated buddy cop
comedy film produced by Walt Disney Animation Studios and the sequel to Zootopia (2016).
Directed by Jared Bush and Byron Howard and written by Bush, the film stars Ginnifer Goodwin, Jason Bateman, Shakira, Idris Elba, Alan Tudyk, Nate Torrence, Don Lake, Bonnie Hunt, and Jenny Slate
reprising their roles from the first film, with Ke Huy Quan, Fortune Feimster, Andy Samberg, David Strathairn, Patrick Warburton, Quinta Brunson, and Danny Trejo joining the cast.
It once again follows Judy Hopps and Nick Wilde, this time as they pursue a reptile named
Gary De'Snake across Zootopia and try to clear their names after being framed.
Zootopia 2 premiered at El Capitan Theatre in Hollywood, Los Angeles on November
13, 2025, and was released in the United States on November 26.
The film received positive reviews from critics and has grossed $1.744 billion worldwide, becoming the second-highest-grossing animated film, the second-highest-grossing film of 2025, the
ninth-highest grossing film of all time, the highest grossing film from Walt Disney Animation Studios, and the highest-grossing American-produced animated film of all time.
The film received nominations for Best Animated Feature at the
Golden Globes, Critics' Choice, and Academy Awards.
It additionally received a nomination for Cinematic and Box
Office Achievement at the Golden Globes.
The film explores themes of snake, bunny, fox, cop, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and mind_bending.